(Leonard:)However briefly.
(Sheldon:)Do you think this possibility
will be hindered...
(Sheldon:)...when she discovers your Luke Skywalker
"no more tears" shampoo?
(Leonard:)It's Darth Vader shampoo.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Leonard:)Luke Skywalker's the conditioner.
- Wait till you see this.
- It's fantastic. Unbelievable.
(Leonard:)See what?
(Howard:)It's a Stephen Hawking lecture from MIT
in 1974.
This isn't a good time.
[IMITATING COMPUTERIZED VOICE]
It's before he became...
...a creepy computer voice.
- That's great, you guys have to go.
- Why?
- It's just not a good time.
- Leonard has a lady over.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Yeah, right.
Your grandmother back in town?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Leonard:)And she's not a lady,
she's just a new neighbor.
(Howard:)Hang on, there really is a lady here?
- Uh-huh.
- And you want us out...
(Howard:)...because you're anticipating coitus?
- I'm not anticipating coitus.
- So she's available for coitus?